Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 1 and District 1 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 1 Locals, 2.
  - Local 163
    - Local 163 Incoming Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Raymond Stout, March 2, 1949; 14.
      - Fitzgerald to Rhodes Regarding Factionalism, November 8, 1949; 15.
      - Fitzgerald Telegram to Stout, et. al. Regarding Factionalism, November 8, 1949; 16.
      - Fitzgerald to Loveleen Howlette Regarding Factionalism, November 23, 1949; 17.
      - Russ Nixon to Asbury Regarding PAC, November 12, 1947; 18.
      - David Ratner Telegram to Rhodes, February 24, 1948; 19.
      - Ratner to Rhodes Regarding Supplies, March 11, 1948; 20.
      - Henry Rhine to Rhodes Regarding Inter-union Rivalry with IUE and Grievances, July 10, 1951; 21.
      - Benjamin Riskin to William Hall Regarding Union Label, December 7, 1948; 22.
      - Riskin to Rhodes Regarding Staff Finances, February 16, 1951; 23.
      - Riskin to Loveleen Richardson Regarding Staff Finances, March 1, 1951; 24.
      - Riskin to Rhodes Regaridng Unemployment with Riskin Memo to James Matles, April 16, 1951; 25.
      - Lloyd Vaughan to Rhodes Regarding Virginia Congress of Industrial Organizations, November 3, 1948; 26.
    - Local 163 Outgoing Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - William Asbury to Julius Emspak Regarding PAC, October 23, 1947; 1.
      - Asbury to Emspak Regarding PAC, November 5, 1947; 2.
      - Asbury to Emspak Regarding PAC, March 20, 1948; 3.
      - Asbury to Bill Cahn Regarding Publicity, February 21, 1949; 4.
      - William Brinkley Regarding Finances, Dues Check-off and IUE Inter-union Rivalry with June 20, 1950, Henry Rhine Letter to David Ratner, June 15, 1950; 5.
      - Dock Clark to Julius Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, July 1947; 6.
      - Clark to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 1947; 7.
      - Clark to Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 22, 1948; 8.
      - Bernice Gillette to Benjamin Riskin Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Unemployment, April 4, 1951; 9.
      - William Grimsley to Emspak Regarding Publicity, February 18, 1948; 10.
      - William Hall to Emspak Regarding Union Label, November 30, 1948; 11.
      - Hall to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and 1949 UE Convention, October 4, 1949; 12.
      - Loveleen Howlette to Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Finances, November 17, 1949; 13.
      - Howlette to I. Duke Aunet Regarding Staff Finances with February 17, 1951, Aunet Letter to David Schribner, February 13, 1951; 14.
      - Jack Myers to Emspak Regarding Local 163 Organization, June 1947; 15.
      - Richard Quesenberry to Emspak Regarding Racism and Factionalism with June 16, 1948, J. Jolly Letter to UE News, August 9, 1948; 16.
      - Quesenberry to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Anti-Communism, 1949; 17.
      - George Rhodes to Ratner Regarding Supplies, March 22, 1947; 18.
      - Rhodes to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, January 27, 1948; 19.
      - Rhodes to Ratner Regarding Finances, February 18, 1948; 20.
      - Rhodes to UE Regarding Publicity and Cost of Living with March 14, 1948, Clipping from Southwest Times, March 15, 1948; 21.
      - Rhodes to Emspak Regarding 1948 UE Convention, September 13, 1948; 22.
      - Rhodes to Emspak Regarding 1948 UE Convention and Staff Finances, October 5, 1948; 23.
      - Rhodes to Lloyd Vaughan Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Inter-union Rivalry and Virginia CIO, November 8, 1948; 24.
      - Rhodes to Tracy Martin Regarding Factionalism and Dues Check-off, November 8, 1949; 25.
      - Rhodes to Raymond Stout Regarding Factionalism and Dues Check-off, November 8, 1949; 26.
      - Rhodes to the Peoples National Bank Regarding Factionalism and Finances, November 8, 1949; 27.
      - Rhodes Telegram to Riskin Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, November 8, 1949; 28.
      - Rhodes to Emspak Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, December 2, 1949; 29.
      - Rhodes to Novelty Printing Company Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Finances, December 30, 1949; 30.
      - Rhodes to Fitzgerald Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 10, 1950; 31.
      - Rhodes to Emspak Regarding Finances and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 21, 1950; 32.
      - Rhodes to Emspak Regarding Radio Broadcasts, March 19, 1950; 33.
      - Stout to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism with Letter to James Price, February 11, 1949; 34.
      - Stout to Fitzgerald Regarding Unemployment, February 23, 1949; 35.
      - Local 163 Members to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, July 8, 1948; 36.
      - Local 163 Membership to T.M. Combiths Regarding Local 163 Officer Elections, October 12, 1948; 37.
    - Local 163 Finances, 1947-1949 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      - Charter Supplies, June 16, 1947; 1.
      - Novelty Printing Company Invoice, September 20, 1949; 2.
    - Local 163 Organization, 1947-1948, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph McCann, June 10, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to McCann, June 17, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to James Price, June 17, 1947; 3.
      - Price to Emspak, June 20, 1948; 4.
      - McCann to Emspak, June 23, 1947; 5.
      - Emspak to Price, June 3, 1947; 6.
      - Emspak to McCann, July 3, 1947; 7.
      - Ray Memo to Paula, n.d.; 8.
    - Local 163 Unemployment Compensation Tax, 1951, undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
      - J.A. Hodnett to Local 163, n.d.; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Hodnett, March 15, 1951; 2.
    - Local 163 Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 55)
      - Benjamin Riskin Memo to James Matles Regarding Unemployment and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 16, 1951; 1.
      - Mary Whitehead to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 25, 1951; 2.
    - Local 163 Newspapers, Family News, June 1951 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Local 163 Leaflets, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 57)
      - "Special Notice", June 12, 1951; 1.
      - "Notice", June 1951; 2.
    - Local 163 Newspaper Clipping, July 1, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Local 163 Press Releases, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 59)
      - IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Plant Tour, January 10, 1950; 1.
      - Membership Meeting, NAACP and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 10, 1950; 2.
  - Local 165
    - Local 165 710 Forms, 1966-1975 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Local 166
    - Local 166 Formigli Corporation Strike, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Local 168
    - Local 168 Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Local 170
    - Local 170 Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Local 170 Legislative Committee and Political Action, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Local 171
    - Local 171 Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Local 172
    - Local 172 Wilnot Engineering Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Local 173
    - Local 173 Dynamic Products Strike, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Local 174
    - Local 174 SMS/Cargo Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Local 174 Year End Statements, 1981-1986 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Local 175
    - Local 175 Argo Charter, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Local 520P
    - Local 520P Organization, 1951, undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
      - Gene Derrickson to Julius Emspak, June 4, 1951; 1.
      - Emspak to Derrickson, June 5, 1951; 2.
      - Herman Morris to Emspak, June 11, 1951; 3.
      - Emspak to Morris, June 25, 1951; 4.
      - Emspak to James Price, June 25, 1951; 5.
      - Emspak to Derrickson, June 25, 1951; 6.
      - Ray Memo, n.d.; 7.
  - Local Constitutions
    - District 1 Local Constitutions, 1942-1950 (Box 10, Folder 73-74)